// Contains the questions and answers for the guided form

var planQuestions = [
    {
        question: "Type of Usage",
        answers: ['Self', 'Dedicate']
    },
    {
        question: "Exporting 3D formats",
        answers: ['Yes (GLB, USDZ)', 'Yes (GLB, USDZ, OBJ, GLTF)','Custom']
    },
    {
        question: "Collaboration",
        answers: ['None', 'Annotation', 'Annotation, Discussion, Drawing', 'Custom']
    },
    {
        question: "Embed and sharing",
        answers: ['None', 'Yes', 'Custom']
    },
    {
        question: "Apple Vision Pro",
        answers: ['Limited', 'Yes', 'Custom']
    },
    {
        question: "Storage Size",
        answers: ['1GB', '5GB', '10GB', 'Custom']
    },
    {
        question: "AI Optimization",
        answers: ['None', 'Yes (first 3 free)', 'Custom']
    },
    {
        question: "Usage Data & Analytics",
        answers: ['None', 'Yes', 'Advanced']
    },
    {
        question: "Security & Compliance (ISO 27001)",
        answers: ['Yes', 'Advanced']
    },
    {
        question: "Support",
        answers: ['Basic', 'Email Support', 'Priority Email - Slack', 'Custom SLA']
    }
]